{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878715260","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878715259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878715493","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878715493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878716466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878716466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878717754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878717754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878720736","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878720735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878721587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878721586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878721908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878721907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878723155","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878723155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878726672","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878726671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878727672","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878727671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878727933","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878727933"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878728889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878728888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878731794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878731793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878732833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878732833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878733311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878733311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878737890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878737888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878738005","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878738005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 43cf2569-7393-4f59-b4f9-715d587172cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878748955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878748954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" ed752b70-6165-43b4-9c2f-5dfd06a35923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878752682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878752682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" ed752b70-6165-43b4-9c2f-5dfd06a35923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878752853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878752853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" ed752b70-6165-43b4-9c2f-5dfd06a35923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878753011","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878753011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" ed752b70-6165-43b4-9c2f-5dfd06a35923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878758869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878758869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" ed752b70-6165-43b4-9c2f-5dfd06a35923"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878773937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878773936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878777402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878777402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878777855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878777855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878779379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878779378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkulima"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878784566","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878784565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878785574","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878785573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878791612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878791611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878792497","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878792497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878798811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878798811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878799762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878799762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakulima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878805043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878805042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878806180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878806180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878827625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878827624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878828530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878828530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878834750","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878834750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" pe"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878914502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878914502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878973185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878973184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878974153","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878974151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878975500","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878975499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878976227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878976226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_buibui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878983551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878983547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878987016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878987015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878989533","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878989532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878991763","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878991762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878993034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878993031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549878999231","data":{"timestamp":" 1549878999228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879001058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879001057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879002253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879002252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879008600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879008600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879010183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879010183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879017441","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879017440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879019083","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879019083"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879025268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879025268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879026690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879026689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879027185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879027185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anaoga"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879032338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879032338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879033278","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879033278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879034262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879034262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879034896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879034895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kutembea"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879040228","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879040227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879042545","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879042545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879044104","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879044103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879044521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879044521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_parachichi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chi"," userResponse":" chi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879049951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879049951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879050923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879050922"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879051512","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879051512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879052009","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879052009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879054211","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879054210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879062827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879062826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879069210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879069209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" d3a75659-474b-4edb-a0ad-e456c9316dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_barabara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879139392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879139392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879145191","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879145190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879149270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879149270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879155449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879155449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879159564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879159564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879162746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879162746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879172541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879172541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879178979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879178979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879183498","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879183498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mwanamke"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879245877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879245877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879250472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879250472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879256087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879256086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879260442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879260441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879265482","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879265480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879269769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879269768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879273224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879273223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879281665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879281665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879283019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879283019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kifungua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879306573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879306573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879307283","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879307283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879316905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879316905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879324204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879324204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879327774","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879327774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879331087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879331087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879339644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879339644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879348700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879348700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879358239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879358239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879365389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879365389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879368207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879368206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879371067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879371067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_pilipili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879400972","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879400972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879405552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879405551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879414105","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879414104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879419699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879419699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879424941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879424940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879428798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879428798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879437556","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879437555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879442695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879442694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879444753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879444752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879451102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879451101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_niruhusu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879478549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879478548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879483586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879483585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879490682","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879490681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879495184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879495183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879500203","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879500202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879504538","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879504537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879508811","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879508810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879510228","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879510227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879522854","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879522853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879526780","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879526779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879529329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879529329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879536587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879536586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879544691","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879544690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879549612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879549611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879555571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879555571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879559154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879559154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879572256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879572256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879574299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879574298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879575756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879575755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879581420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879581420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879584817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879584816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879592147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879592146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879593646","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879593645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879596584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879596584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879605197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879605197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879609570","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879609570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_alifuata"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879648986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879648986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879652190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879652189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879660056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879660055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879665707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879665707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879670816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879670815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879677707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879677706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879684803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879684803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879689197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879689196"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nimefika"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879703941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879703936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879707374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879707373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879709065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879709064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879710979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879710978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879713134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879713134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879715039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879715039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879718615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879718614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879720076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879720076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sawasawa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879747213","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879747212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879752138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879752137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879759774","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879759773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879765247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879765246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879773177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879773174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879777820","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879777820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879782772","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879782771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879787026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879787025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-8.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879797676","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879797674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879812503","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879812502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879825215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879825213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879836358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879836357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" adfe0a47-e417-4eba-af07-d5753c5a4ac6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-8.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_wakiruka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879854529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879854523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879855260","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879855258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879862355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879862354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879862940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879862939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879870130","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879870128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879870850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879870849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anakula"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879886931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879886925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879887649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879887648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879894853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879894852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879896491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879896489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" so"," userResponse":" so"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879897022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879897020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anasoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879903551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879903549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ba"," userResponse":" ba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879905038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879905037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879914292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879914291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879916897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879916896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879919049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879919049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879919994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879919993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879931370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879931369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879933911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879933910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mi"," userResponse":" mi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879935212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879935211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879942649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879942648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879943373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879943373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_familia"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879951309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879951307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879953217","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879953216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879960403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879960402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879961788","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879961782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879968898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879968896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" che"," userResponse":" che"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879969749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879969749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_alicheza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879975942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879975940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879977325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879977323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879985123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879985120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" na"," userResponse":" na"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879987051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879987050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879994110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879994110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549879995336","data":{"timestamp":" 1549879995335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wanawake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ke"," userResponse":" ke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880002991","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880002990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880004511","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880004511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880005752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880005751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bo"," userResponse":" bo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880006741","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880006733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" da"," userResponse":" da"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880013053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880013050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880015213","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880015210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880016083","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880016081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880017353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880017352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpapai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880023747","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880023745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880025590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880025590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880027444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880027443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880029034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880029033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880034764","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880034763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880036745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880036745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880038824","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880038823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" te"," userResponse":" te"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880040819","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880040819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880042411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880042411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880046399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880046397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549880055981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549880055979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_125143"," gameId":" 310f6d98-9ea3-48a0-8594-088427fca880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_4"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_wakitembea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}